(Sheldon:)Or a Nutter Butter,
if you're in a pinch.
(Penny:)Come on, open it.
I bet it says something great.
(Sheldon:)This is Asian fusion.
(Sheldon:)For all you know,
there's a tiny Chihuahua in here.
(Penny:)Fine, I'll go.
"People tum to you
for guidance and wisdom."
(Penny:)-Yeah, that's a good one.
-No, it's not.
(Penny:)-How is that not good?
-"Tum to you for wisdom?"
(Sheldon:)Clearly, that cookie is mocking you.
(Sheldon:)You'd never hear that kind of sass
from a Nutter Butter.
(Penny:)Since you're paying for dinner,
I'll let that slide. Open yours.
(Sheldon:)-Have you ever paid for a meal?
-Not with money. Read.
"Your warm and fun-loving nature
delights those around you."
(Penny:)Oh, try again.